<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on tdl-jturner</title>
    <link>http://thedigitallink.net/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on tdl-jturner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 16:30:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://thedigitallink.net/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Data and Drinks with DataStax &amp; Confluent</title>
      <link>http://thedigitallink.net/events/2019-10-17-dataanddrinks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 16:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thedigitallink.net/events/2019-10-17-dataanddrinks/</guid>
      <description>Date : October 17, 2019 Location: Seattle, WA Event: Data and Drinks with DataStax &amp;amp; Confluent  Abstract Discussion about how T-Mobile has leveraged DataStax to overcome data challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Cassandra Users: Apache Cassandra At T-Mobile</title>
      <link>http://thedigitallink.net/events/2019-10-09-cassandraseattleusers-t-mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 18:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thedigitallink.net/events/2019-10-09-cassandraseattleusers-t-mobile/</guid>
      <description>Date : October 9, 2019 Location: Seattle, WA Event: Seattle Cassandra Users Video: YouTube Slides: SlideShare  Abstract T-Mobile is using Cassandra to back many of our national platforms including device activations, eSim management, bill payments, and T-Mobile Digits. In this talk we will discuss our journey as we migrated away from legacy relational databases and the challenges of having to overcome skill gaps, develop automation, and create tooling to manage our new distributed data system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Cassandra Users: An OSS Java Abstraction Layer for Cassandra</title>
      <link>http://thedigitallink.net/events/2019-06-26-cassandraseattleusers-casquatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 15:38:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thedigitallink.net/events/2019-06-26-cassandraseattleusers-casquatch/</guid>
      <description>Date : June 26, 2019 Location: Seattle, WA Event: Seattle Cassandra Users Slides: SlideShare  Abstract Project Casquatch is a database abstraction layer with code generation designed to streamline Cassandra development. Out of the box it comes pre-tuned with high available policies including load balancing, geo-redundancy, connection pooling, etc., sitting on top of the DataStax driver using native APIs. All of this is abstracted behind the ever prevalent POJO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DataStax Day at the Ballpark</title>
      <link>http://thedigitallink.net/events/2019-06-04-datastaxday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 18:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thedigitallink.net/events/2019-06-04-datastaxday/</guid>
      <description>Date : June 06, 2019 Location: Seattle, WA Event: DataStax Day at the Ballpark  Abstract High level customer experience presentation with Q&amp;amp;A</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DataStax Accelerate: Casquatch</title>
      <link>http://thedigitallink.net/events/2019-05-22-datastaxaccelerate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 15:38:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thedigitallink.net/events/2019-05-22-datastaxaccelerate/</guid>
      <description>Date : May 22, 2019 Location: Washington, DC Event: DataStax Accelerate 2019 Video: YouTube Slides: SlideShare  Abstract Project Casquatch is a database abstraction layer with code generation designed to streamline Cassandra development. Out of the box it comes pre-tuned with high available policies including load balancing, geo-redundancy, connection pooling, etc., sitting on top of the DataStax driver using native APIs. All of this is abstracted behind the ever prevalent POJO.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>